I just finished work around 6 PM, and I'm listening to it again
The part about the little devil Ageha is really interesting (laughs). I'm really praising myself
Are you going to spread that kind of story with a little devil like Ageha?
I was wondering what to start talking about
I was thinking that there isn't enough discussion about
my father's suicide
So, if I had to sum it up in one word, my father is...
The existence of 'nothing' is 'nothing'
I don't know how to put it. Anyway, I'm quiet at home
So, I guess I was around 22 years old, maybe 3 years old
I left home and started working in Tokyo,
but the total time I spent talking with my father until then
was about 2 hours (laughs)
That might be a bit of an exaggeration, though
Probably less than a day
It really makes you think about how little we talked, right?
There aren't any memorable conversations, you know
That's why it's nothing. It was nothing after all
I knew he was a kind person, but...
In the family, he is definitely under his mother's thumb, you know
No, seriously, it's just a really amazing story
It felt like I was being told to at least argue back a little
But you know, the more you argue, the more it comes back to you
What was that saying about getting double the return?
It's not 'handanaki', what was it again?
Is this like Hanzawa Naoki? It's a mental Hanzawa Naoki
And that's why it's hysterical, because it's hysterical Fuwachan,
so what kind of mix is that?
It's a mix, right? It's already a greedy set. It's a greedy set, you know
My mother. Ah, that's why
I think Dad is tired too
Because I get bitten every time. I think that's why he went silent
Yeah, yeah, oh I see, I wonder what that is
Back in elementary school, Tenrikyo
Ah, I said it
You know, we used to dance in the morning and evening
Well, I've already said it, so it doesn't matter,
but I started getting into it
That's right
Oh right, I forgot. I had forgotten, but
It's not that, the story is long, so I'll skip a bit, hmm
That's the kind of dad who, well, committed suicide
I never thought my own parent would commit suicide
I didn't think so. February 2020
Well, that was five years ago. I was like, 'What?!'
So, for a while, I was kind of confused. I was confused, you know
I have to attend a funeral, right? And it's far away in the countryside. It's about two hours from the metropolitan area. It's not that far, though
It's not really that far, or something like that
I felt like it was a bit farther away, but for me, it's far
Two hours. Being jostled around on a train for two hours is torture, and I'm a recluse
Is that really how much you use it?
It's kind of that vibe
So, two hours on the train,
even if it's for my father's funeral, was really a hassle
So maybe I don't have to go
I didn't love them that much, you know? It was like that. What a messed up person
Well, if you think about it, I am a messed up person
But, you know, I thought to myself that I couldn't just not show up, so I reconsidered and went out
So, it's about the psychological depiction during the funeral and stuff
It takes a lot of time, so I'll skip that part. Yeah, in the end, I thought it was good that I went. Of course, that's true (laughs)
But still, it's a matter of not overthinking it
Yeah, I did overthink it. It was a hassle, and I didn't really like it that much,
so I thought you guys could just handle it on your own
Honestly, that's how I felt
So, after the funeral,
my father's figure keeps flashing in my mind
It really keeps flashing. The changes in his mind leading up to his suicide, you know?
That kind of thing really hits you in the heart
It's really coming. My house is in the countryside, you know
It's quite spacious. It's about 1,000 tsubo
I'm not sure
if 1,000 tsubo
is considered spacious,
but it's pretty big, you know
The place where the suicide happened, um, it's like a storage area for agricultural machinery
It's what you might call a row house
It's quite large and made of corrugated metal
When I say large, I mean it's about 20 meters long
Well, it's in a place where farming tools and things like threshers are kept
So, there's a small house at the edge of the property,
and the father is currently living about 100 meters away from that house
It might not even be 100 meters
I'm not sure, but it's around that distance
Up to that tenement where the suicide happened,
I imagine what kind of feelings I had while walking there, and it comes to me, you know
Because, even if I had resolved to commit suicide,
it's tough, right? Yeah, I think it's tough
But we can overcome that
What I'm trying to say is...
In the end, it was what drove my father to suicide
So, what I mean is
In the end, I think it was all about not wanting to be a burden to my family
Yeah, so when I talked to my brother about it at that time,
"I felt like I had no value in life anymore," or something like that
It seems like they were mumbling about that. Yeah
Right, I think it's pretty amazing
Because, in essence, it's like dying
for someone else
Even though it's not exactly someone else
Dying for family. Yeah, with the sole intention of not wanting to burden the family, they ended up dying
It's really heartbreaking, I think it's a painful heart
Hmm, it's like I realized you died for me
Now, it's really hitting me, and when I look back...
Well, I'm just living in decadence, aren't I? I think it's bad
and I need to do something about it, but...
Well, it's more like I can't do anything because I've become so lazy
Well, what should I do? I don't even know what I should do
I was troubled and troubled
So what I did was start a diet (laughs)
Like, a diet there?
Where and how do you connect to make it a diet? Something like that
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I think it would be interesting if we traced that out,
but the story there is long. And it's long and interesting
In my mind. That's why
That's that, and there's no need to talk about it separately. Yeah, it's fine, though
Hmm, about that father of yours, um,
how should I put it?
When I stood at the funeral, you know
Dad was already so skinny
Hmm, he was really skinny
The reason is that his swallowing function, in other words,
the ability to swallow food, seemed to have decreased
It seems that due to that, I couldn't eat food,
it became difficult to eat, and I ended up in a situation
like being emaciated and having a rectal prolapse
A rectal prolapse is when the intestines come out from the anus,
and you have to hurriedly push them back in
While experiencing that feeling of becoming more and more useless, I think the meaning of my existence, well,
you know, is probably something like depression
I think I was really troubled and tried to commit suicide
But the circumstances leading up to that were all about not wanting to burden my family. It was all love, really
I was loved that much. It's just overwhelming
I mean, my dad was amazing; he overcame the fear of death purely out of love
I thought it was amazing
Dad, you're cool, yeah
For the first time, towards my father
I felt a sense of respect, you know
Yeah, it's like, Dad is so cool
I mean, he's a samurai, right? It's like he's at a dead end and then there's that whole seppuku vibe
It's really the spirit of a samurai
When you say 'Samurai Spirits', I think people who know about that
early adopter from some weird text site
would burst out laughing
Well, it was something like the early adopter, and I was making fun of it
Actually, robots have developed quite a bit too
That's fine, but you know...
It's the spirit of the samurai. It sounds completely different, though
I thought I saw the spirit of the samurai
It's Shibata Katsuie, right?
Like, look at my guts, or something
Pulling out my guts, like, boom, guts explosion, you know? Oh,
it's like a man's (otoko) way of dying,
like a samurai, you know?
I thought, for the first time, how cool it is and how amazing it is
Hmm, yeah
It's like, 'Son, watch how I die.'
It's like the final teaching
I don't have the first
teaching (laughs),
but I only have the last teaching
The last teaching is also silent, but isn't it too quiet, like, too taciturn? I think so,
but how should I put it?
It feels like being hit with tacit knowledge, you know?
It's like saying, 'Just watch how I die.'
Wow, that's really cool
Dad, is that how you overcome the fear of death?
That's amazing, right?
Thinking about it that way, I respect Dad
It's not like I ever really disliked him
I always thought he was a kind person
I thought I was a weak person
To be honest, I'm too weak towards my mother
I wish you would rebel a little, you know?
It's like, you should dominate a bit, you know, like a man
While thinking about those cries from the heart,
I find myself looking at my father
Is there going to be a big turnaround at the very end?
It's that kind of delightful surprise
Yeah, right, I thought it was amazing. But on the other hand, there’s this image of a weak person, um, like a father figure, you know?
Thinking about that,
In that situation, trying to escape from the pain, trying to escape
In conclusion, I think that the idea of suicide
as an escape might be closer to the true nature of things
But when I think about it like that,
It's like, that's me,
right? Like, that's me right now
For the first time, I thought, 'I'm my father's child.' It's a strange connection,
but I am definitely my dad's kid
It's me, you know
But that escape isn't 100%
an escape, right?
I think I'm wrapped in kindness. I think I'm wrapped in love. So,
In the end, I get caught up in my worries,
and it makes me feel a bit depressed and makes me want to run away, but,
But you know, that's kindness taking off
It's like kindness is taking off
Kindness starts. It's overflowing with love for others. That's right
So, for love, I'm running away
It's a runaway love, isn't it?
That's kind of like that
There are definitely songs like that. I don't know, but there must be something
A love escape. Should I Google it? A love escape. A love escape
A love memory? A love love escape. Who was it? Ah, a foreigner, come out Wikipedia
Wikipedia. Hmm, I don't think so
It feels kind of like a movie. There are too many love escapes, how many are there?
Is everyone interested in such a theme? I wonder what it is
Netflix, a drama film from West Germany and Finland in 1986
Wasn't there a song about a love escape? A love escape song. Akashi and Secret, who is that? Is the love escape someone really obscure?
Who is this? I wonder if there's no song like that by Secret
Misora Ai. Escape, it's Akari Kito, right?
That's the Nezuko from Demon Slayer, right? It's kind of silly
Yeah. I don't watch it
A love escape, huh? I guess it doesn't really matter,
I got off topic
Um, what was it? Right, it comes from a weakness of the heart, but it starts with love, doesn't it?
Love for children and such
It's like the love for a mother
that leads to the result of suicide
So, you see, suicide is like that
I couldn't really believe it. We went to the funeral, and then, sure enough,
there was a faint mark around the neck, like a diagonal, um, what do you call it? It had a faint purple hue, probably something the funeral director tried to cover up with makeup for the deceased
Even so, there was that faint mark, you know,
like what you often see in 'The Women of the Forensic Science Lab' or whatever it's called
Is it called a linear mark (correctly, it's 'sakujo-kon')? I forgot,
but it was something like that,
like a hanging mark, and I needed to get a family register
When I got my family register, it was recorded as hanging suicide
Well, the term hanging suicide is written with this really difficult kanji, and yeah,
it's just one of those complicated characters
Looking at that, I thought, wow,
I really did hang myself to death
I wasn't present at the scene of that hanging suicide, so I didn't really understand it
So, um, I guess my perception of that was kind of vague
At the funeral, or rather, before the funeral, during the wake,
they tell you to clean the body with a cloth or something, right? (That's what the funeral home staff instructs you to do.)
At that time, you know, I realized again, yeah
Yeah, my legs were super thin at that time, like, with legs this thin
I was walking for about 70 meters
I wonder what I was thinking while walking, you know, I imagine it
But no matter how I imagine it, only kind words come to mind
I was that kind of person
who probably thought kind things
It's heartbreaking, you know
I'm really sorry, Dad, and my feelings are incredibly strong
No, I really caused a lot of trouble for you, Dad
It's mainly a financial hassle, you know
I really regret not being able to apologize for that,
and it's been weighing on my mind
Starting a diet,
huh? (laughs) What a punchline
What kind of development is this?
Yeah, that's the kind of story it is
So it's amazing. You've awakened, right?
I know it's a bit self-serving to say,
but you know that moment in Dragon Ball
when Krillin gets killed, right?
It's like, 'Krillin!' Boom!
That's the trigger for becoming a Super Saiyan
It's probably when Krillin was killed, right?
Well, I don't remember exactly, but you know
That's the kind of brain-internal Krillin I have
My brain-internal Krillin was killed by my father's suicide
And then, like, boom! It's like awakening into a Super Saiyan
Well, it feels like I'm awakening
Also, what are you doing, by the way?
Yeah. No, but seriously, it was developing a lot inside me
Only in my head, yeah
How the body is already a lazy human
As for the body, it's so slow. So, how many minutes have passed?
How many minutes have passed?
So it's been 20 minutes. I see
Should I wrap it up here? I've talked about the mental image of Krillin
So, is everything generally okay? I'll bring up the finer details later, but essentially, it was the trigger for my suicidal thoughts that made me start thinking I needed to change my way of living; that's the origin, right?
And that's how I got to where I am now
Well, the developments from the diet are interesting too
I really want to talk about that, I can't help it
If I start talking about that, it will be really long
It might take about 5 hours. Or maybe not even 5 hours
Well, my father's death was shocking. I mean, it was shocking, but at the same time, it wasn't
It gradually hits me, and when I imagine those last few moments of my father, you know...
I can't help but cry, cry, it's just how it is
It's like I remember my father's kindness, you know?
At the same time, I think,
'Hey, this is what
it means to be a man.'
What are you up to?
Like, my son
I really felt and appreciated that strong patriarchal message
It's like I've regained my respect for my father
I was really happy about that. It might be a bit strange to say that respect came after contemplating suicide,
but it really resonated with my heart. Until I truly changed
It has taken me five years to get to this point
Well, it hasn't changed even now
My mental state is really something
It's always spinning in my head
So, in my mind, I'm making progress
The body isn't keeping up,
so it's designed for laziness,
that's how it feels
At the very end, a huge turnaround, full respect for my father. Wow, this person is amazing, really great
Being able to respect my father
Hmm, it's about the patriarchal aspect
It's something I can respect. Hmm, that's why
I've been thinking about it for a long time
If my father had a motherly personality and my mother had a fatherly personality,
how much easier would that have been? I mean, when I was going to advance my studies, I told my mother,
My mother would do everything she could for me
If my father, with his strange obsession with academic credentials, was actually smart,
It's like, 'Study hard here and go to a good university,' which is a patriarchal approach,
right? If it was like that,
it would be like a mother who just obediently follows a kind and quiet father
There are times when I really think about how much better
it could have been
Yeah, that's really important
That paternal and maternal nature were completely opposite, you know
The reversal of paternal and maternal roles. It's something important
I'm doing it while taking notes, you know
It's for my own use, and I plan to share it with others later, but that's fine, right? Hehehe
Such a casual way to approach skills. I can only think about the requirements
I'm just speaking off the top of my head. That's right
The injustice of fatherhood feels different. It feels like a reversal of fatherhood
It's turning into a really long story
But I want to dig deeper into it, that's true, but you know, my dad is going bald
My mother has a balding look. Yeah, that's right. She's balding, so it's a young baldness
It seems like she started losing hair when she was young, and I think that's become one of my father's complexes. It's related to women and various other things, so it's like a young baldness complex. It's not something to take notes on
Dad has a young baldness complex
That's also an important factor
Hmm, that's amazing
Themes keep coming up one after another
The conversation isn't over yet
Writing the document isn't finished either
Isn't it endless
that my work never seems to end?
The more I talk, the more themes come up
Ah, well, that's going to make the conversation long
I'll cut it off around here
Well, I guess it won't come out anymore for now
It's going to be okay, right?
Hmm, well even if it does come out,
we'll talk about it again later
Hmm, I ended up talking for another 25 minutes like that
I'm sorry, well then